Welcome to LuminFlow.
An AI-powered audit transparency platform,
built on the COSO 2013 framework.
The Dashboard delivers real-time visibility
into audit progress and control coverage.
Track PBC completion and aggregated risk
scores across the engagement.
Role-based views adapt instantly for
Auditors, Partners, and CFOs.
A live heatmap, stepper, and activity
timeline keep every stakeholder aligned.
TraceMap visualizes the COSO 2013
three-level objective hierarchy.
An interactive audit tree connects
objectives, risks, and controls.
AI Insight decomposes strategic goals
into testable, traceable controls.
A radar chart benchmarks coverage
across multiple audit dimensions.
HeatLens unifies the full risk landscape
with the Risk Control Matrix.
Tune weights for inherent risk and
control effectiveness in real time.
Multi-factor scoring captures the true
residual exposure no single metric can.
SampleLens recommends optimal sample
sizes through AI-driven analysis.
Supports monetary unit and attribute
sampling methodologies.
Tune confidence, tolerable, and expected
deviation rates with full transparency.
Event-driven reinforcement expands
samples when control risk rises.
PBCView centralizes Provided-By-Client
document management end to end.
AI auto-generates tailored PBC lists
by industry and audit process.
Overdue alerts and reminder emails
accelerate every client response.
Progress tracked by control area
streamlines auditor-client exchange.
NarrativeLens turns raw findings into
structured narratives via generative AI.
Key points are extracted automatically
and prepared for review.
A three-step flow routes drafts through
Submit, Manager, and Partner sign-off.
Human-AI collaboration safeguards
every narrative's audit quality.
ImpactSimulator models the outcome
of any control deficiency.
A force-directed graph traces how risk
propagates through connected nodes.
Quantify potential financial loss
and regulatory penalty exposure.
AI ranks remediation priority
by projected business impact.
TeamPanel governs a multi-role
permission matrix for the engagement.
From Audit Manager to Client Liaison,
visibility is scoped per dataset.
The AI assistant answers natural-language
audit queries instantly.
Analyze risks, generate sampling plans,
or explain COSO principles on demand.
API data integrations are managed
from one unified console.
Every module connects into one
continuous, end-to-end workflow.
Data flows across planning, execution,
and assessment without friction.
RESTful APIs open LuminFlow to ERP,
GRC, and external audit systems.
From planning to sign-off, LuminFlow
unifies every audit signal.
Faster cycles, sharper insight,
and defensible evidence at every step.
Audit transparency, redefined.
Step into LuminFlow and discover
intelligent assurance in action.